shasso.biz 2014-07-20

# OffGamers Online Game Store - MMO Game, PC Game CD Key and Game Card Store. | Privacy Policy | OffGamers

| 

OffGamers respects your privacy and works hard to safeguard the privacy of your personal data. We realize that the exciting growth of the Internet and online services raise questions concerning the nature, use and confidentiality of information collected about consumers. We want you to know that we apply our long-standing commitment of safeguarding privacy to our online and Internet activities.

In addition to the general privacy concerns, please note that we collect, store and handle personal information of individuals in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 (“PDPA”) and the laws of Malaysia.

Please read the Privacy Statement below to understand how we use the personal information we may collect from you. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

By providing your Personal Information to us, you are consenting to this Privacy Statement and the collection, use, access, transfer, storage and processing of your personal information as described in this Privacy Statement.

## Information We Collect From You

We value your trust in providing us your personal information. OffGamers does not share, disclose or sell any personally-identifiable information (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) collected online on OffGamers' sites with other unaffiliated companies or organizations for non-OffGamers marketing purposes. Because this information is a critical part of our business, it would be treated like our other assets in the context of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding. 

## We Are Responsible For Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. OffGamers also does not market to, or knowingly collect personal information from, children under age of 13 on any sites of the company. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information. 

## When Can We Collect Your Personal Information?

We may collect personal information directly from you when you:- 

  * communicate with us (for example when you submit an application form to become our customer, or when you contact us for any enquiries including by calling our customer service)
  * register or subscribe for a specific Product and/or Service or our publications (for example, newsletters)
  * participate in any of our surveys
  * enter into or participate in any competitions, contests or loyalty programs run/organized by OffGamers
  * register interest and/or request for information of (through our online portals or other available channels) or subscribe to our Products and/or Services
  * respond to any marketing materials we send out
  * visit or browse our websites
  * lodge a complaint with us
  * provide feedback to us (for example via our websites or in hard copy)

Other than personal information obtained from you directly (as detailed above), we may also obtain your personal information from third parties we deal with or are connected with you (credit reference agencies or financial institutions), and from such other sources where you have given your consent for the disclosure of information relating to you, and/or where otherwise lawfully permitted. 

## How Can We Collect Your Personal Information?

OffGamers collects information online by asking you for it, for example, when you order a service, apply for a job, or respond to a survey, offer or other promotion. A customer's name, address (postal and e-mail) and telephone number are the most important pieces of information, but we might request other information, based on, for example, the service(s) being ordered or promoted.

**Cookies** : OffGamers uses cookies to provide you the best user experience on our website. For further information about cookies please click [here.]()

**Content** : You also provide us information in content you post to the website. Your content (such as reviews, photos and videos) and metadata about your content will be viewed by other users. OffGamers can, but has no obligation, to monitor your content you post on the website. We can remove any information you post for any reason or no reason.

**Payment Method** : You will also be asked to submit Personal Information depending on the payment method you choose when accessing, purchasing or subscribing to one of our products or services. For example, if you choose to pay for a product/service by credit card, you will be required to provide us the name of your credit card issuer, credit card number, billing address, CVV number, and expiration date.

**Log Files** : When you use the website, our servers automatically record certain information sent by your web browser. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the website, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, mobile carrier, and other such information.

**Geo-Location Information** : When you use the website by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store “location data,” which may include GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device.

**Third Party Tools** : OffGamers uses third party analytics tools, to help understand use of the website. Many of these tools collect the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. These analytics tools also receive this information and their use of it is governed by their privacy policy. 

## How Can We Use Your Information

OffGamers uses the personally-identifiable information collected online principally to provide you with the service(s) you have ordered and to let you know about other offerings which may be of interest to you. Postal and e-mail address information, for example, enables communication about services offered and ordered, as well as the proper provisioning and billing of those services. At any point of time, should you feel the need to opt-out future communications with OffGamers, options are given within to exclude those communicated messages to you.

We also provide personally-identifiable online information in response to subpoenas and other legal demands, and where we believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against individuals who may be endangering public safety or interfering with OffGamers' services, or with our customers' or others' use of them. 

## What We Request From You

We request you to provide us accurate and complete information about yourself and any other person whose personal information you provide us and for updating when it becomes incorrect or out of date by contacting us.This obligation is a condition to the provision of our Products and/or Services to you and/or any other person authorized or permitted by you or your organization/company to use the Products and/or Services. 

## We Promise Privacy & Security

Both of us together play an important role in protecting against online fraud. You should be careful that any information including your User ID, Password, Security Device and/or Security Code are not compromised by ensuring that you do not knowingly or accidentally share, provide or facilitate unauthorized use of it. Do not share your User ID, Password, Security Device and/or Security Code or allow access or use of it/them by others.

At OffGamers, we use encryption, firewalls and other technology and security procedures to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or improper use. For example, you will note that while using some features of the OffGamers's web site you will need to submit a password or some other type of authenticating information. 

## Disclosure of Your Information (If Needed)

When you have provided Personal Information to us for a particular purpose, we may disclose your information to other companies that we have engaged to assist us in fulfilling your request. This may include, but is not limited to, fulfillment houses, billing services, transaction managers, credit verification services, and other third-party service providers. We may also disclose any of your Personal Information to law enforcement or other appropriate third parties in connection with criminal investigations, investigation of fraud, infringement of intellectual property rights, or other suspected illegal activities, or as otherwise may be required by applicable law, or, as we deem necessary in our sole discretion, in order to protect the legitimate legal interests of OffGamers. 

## Notices to the Changes in Privacy Policies

OffGamers reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by notifying registered users via e-mail of the existence of a new Privacy Policy and/or posting the new Privacy Policy on OffGamers. All changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective when posted, and your continued use of OffGamers, product or service after the posting will constitute your acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes. 

|   
---|---|---
